<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollApp</string>
    <string name="textview">
        <b> Computer programming</b> is the process of designing and building an executable computer program to accomplish a specific computing result or to perform a specific task. Programming involves tasks such as: analysis, generating algorithms, profiling algorithms/ accuracy and resource consumption, and the implementation of algorithms in a chosen programming language (commonly referred to as coding).[1][2] \nThe source code of a program is written in one or more languages that are intelligible to programmers, rather than machine code, which is directly executed by the central processing unit. The purpose of programming is to find a sequence of instructions that will automate the performance of a task (which can be as complex as an operating system) on a computer, often for solving a given problem. Proficient programming thus often requires expertise in several different subjects, including knowledge of the application domain, specialized algorithms, and formal logic.

Tasks accompanying and related to programming include: testing, debugging, source code maintenance, implementation of build systems, and management of derived artifacts, such as the machine code of computer programs. \nThese might be considered part of the programming process, but often the term software development is used for this larger process with the term programming, implementation, or coding reserved for the actual writing of code. Software engineering combines engineering techniques with software development practices. \nReverse engineering is a related process used by designers, analysts and programmers to understand and re-create/re-implement.[3]:3
        This project  (CALCULATOR   PROJECT) is written in C language. This project allows you input any data on which various mathematical operations can be performed.
It is like a mini calculator which can be used for teaching kids .
This project consists of a GRAPHICAL  INTERFACE  due to which kids might be attract towards it.
Following project allows you to ADD , SUBTRACT , MULTIPLY , DIVIDE numbers.\n
You get the output with ongoing calculations step by step so that student understand it better.\n
Turbo C  version 2.0 is used in this game. Turbo C is a discontinued Integrated Development Environment and compiler for the C programming language from Borland. First introduced in 1987, it was noted for its integrated development environment, small size, fast compile speed, comprehensive manuals and low price .In May 1990, Borland replaced Turbo C with Turbo C++.\n
        C is a general-purpose, imperative computer programming language, supporting structured programming, lexical variable scope and recursion, while a static type system prevents many unintended operations. By design, C provides constructs that map efficiently to typical machine instructions, and therefore it has found lasting use in applications that had formerly been coded in assembly language, including operating systems, as well as various application software for computers ranging from supercomputers to embedded systems.\n

C was originally developed by Dennis Ritchie between 1969 and 1973 at Bell Labs, and used to re-implement the Unix operating system. It has since become one of the most widely used programming languages of all time.\n

C is an imperative procedural language. It was designed to be compiled using a relatively straightforward compiler, to provide low-level access to memory, to provide language constructs that map efficiently to machine instructions, and to require minimal run-time support. Despite its low-level capabilities, the language was designed to encourage cross-platform programming

    </string>


</resources>